Crysis a stolen car with a young child trapped inside a dramatic change three different people carjacking long the way old is playing out on live television
孤岛危机偷来的汽车与一个年轻的孩子被困一个戏剧性的变化里面三个不同的人劫车长的路旧是打出来的电视直播
nightly news
晚间新闻
images according to the Chinese show three objects that seem to be floating in the ocean large pieces 4359 feed 5662 and 78 by 72
根据中国图片显示，似乎是漂浮在海洋中大块料4359 5662 78 72三个对象
importantly dentify does being in a very area of the South China Sea over which this plane was last reported halfway between Malaysia and Vietnam the corners put the record of South Vietnam and this is an area
重要的是dentify并在中国南海一个非常面积是指这架飞机最后一次报道马来西亚和越南的中间弯道把南越的记录，这是一个地区
ships planes and helicopters from a dozen babies again images show plane debris the plane ever made
船舶飞机和直升机从十几婴儿再次图片显示飞机残骸做过飞机
the Strait of Malacca Malaysia military has been suggested over the past two days
马六甲马来西亚军事​​海峡曾有人建议在过去两天
the development comes as the define of searches on today grew up 3 1000 square miles to the east of Malaysia the South China Sea in the Gulf of Thailand to the west the Strait of Malacca and the atom and see what the Indian Navy join the search for suing the theory that the plane did double back
发展自带搜索作为定义在今天长大了3千平方英里的马来西亚中国南海在泰国湾，西面马六甲海峡和原子东部，看看印度海军加入搜寻起诉的理论，这架飞机也加倍奉还
I get to depict the wreckage would a mediately refocus this investigation what caused the crash mechanical human air or something else
我得到描绘残骸将一个治疗中重新调整本次调查是什么原因造成飞机坠毁的机械人空气或别的东西
I talk to the Fox a flight radar 24 in stock home earlier today ver radar data shows at the plane beta swype John to the right part of the normal flight to Beijing and then it dropped off the radar the transporter stop transmitting of the crew stop responding to Radio cost
我跟福克斯飞行雷达24家股票今天早些时候版本的雷达数据显示在平面公测的Swype约翰正常航班到北京的右边部分，然后下车雷达船员停止响应的转运停止传输以成本电台
US military intelligence agencies tell em BC news Chinese images importantly the Chinese have been very vocal in their criticism and how to search has been conducted
美国军方情报机构告诉电磁省新闻中国形象重要的是中国已经非常声乐在他们的批评，以及如何搜索已进行
alright thank you so much and I would join an expert Greg 5 is a former senior Air Safety Director with the National Transportation Safety Board
好吧谢谢你这么多，我会参加的专家格雷格5是一名前高级航空安全主任与国家运输安全委员会
amendments highly experienced and also a veteran pilot Greg thank you for joining us do you believe images of Nursing now late today are showing us the plains record
修订具有丰富经验，也是一个经验丰富的飞行员格雷格感谢您加入我们的行列，你认为护士的形象现在的今天迟到是向我们展示了平原纪录
based on the resolution of these images of skeptical at this point
基于对怀疑这些图像在这一点上分辨率
normal if you have pieces of aircraft or possibly peace the bear crap this large you would expect to see a large debris field cause this is a very large piece of wood pieces of aircraft
正常的，如果你有个飞机或可能和平熊废话这么大，你会希望看到一个大碎片领域的事业，这是一个非常大的一块木头碎片飞机
so you would expect to see not only the the 7472 foot piece of of structure if this is airplane what all the Dupre that would go with a seat cushion seat if the water is in debt
所以你会希望看到的不仅是在7472英尺片结构的，如果这是什么飞机的所有杜普雷会去同一个坐垫座椅，如果水是债务
what you're saying as you're not banking on it so it isn't the wreckage in a plane didn't fack make a turn as we hurt earlier today and we just heard from Tom Costello could we in fact im looking possibly at a criminal investigation here
你的意思是你不指望它，所以它不是残骸在一个平面上并没有法克打个转，因为我们今天早些时候受到伤害，我们刚刚从汤姆·科斯特洛能听到我们其实即时寻找可能在这里刑事调查
think that still has to be considered given the fact that we've had burying information over the last 5 days nothing has been confirmed in the stuff that we thought was confirm some of the information has been physically retracted
认为仍然必须考虑鉴于我们已经埋葬了的信息在最近5天一切都没有在我们认为是确认一些信息的东西被证实已实际收回
so I think we have to wear these the best Gators what have to continue to pursue intentional act of Criminal aspect of it as well as possible
所以我认为我们必须穿这些最好的短吻鳄有什么要继续追求其刑事方面的故意行为，以及可能
so you're saying that you wouldn't Doris data search continues not a long the flight path as we saw these images according to the China as a television news agency that that's where they took the photographs you're saying that you should still be looking in the Indian Ocean
所以你说，你会不会多丽丝数据继续搜索不长的飞行路径，因为我们看到了这些图像根据中国作为一个电视新闻机构，这就是他们把你说的话，你应该还是照片寻找在印度洋
women validate what's that object is that is on a satellite image somebody needs to actually looking identify that as aircraft parkour parts
女验证那是什么对象是在卫星图像需要有人实际上是在寻找确定飞机零部件跑酷
what you can't give up where that radar image with coming from because there are a number of radar points a word very very Furman saying we had this airplane track so you must continue a long bath Pappas wealth and possibly even further
你不能放弃在那里与来自因为有许多雷达未来的雷达图像​​指向一个词非常非常弗曼说我们有这个飞机的航迹所以你必须继续长时间的盆浴帕帕斯财富，甚至可能进一步
much more to talk about is the story develops thank you for your valuables
更多谈论的是故事的发展感谢您的贵重物品
turnout in New York City tonight were there was a desperate search on the way for 9 people still on accounted for after that massive explosion that destroyed two buildings and
出席者在纽约市今晚在那里是在路上绝望的寻找9人仍然入账的巨大的爆炸摧毁了两座建筑物后
tire Mabry hood at least three people are dead scores injure someone in critical condition
轮胎马布里罩至少三个人都死了分数伤害别人，情况危殆
falling hair tonight the fire still so intense extremely difficult at last 70 people that was Phil and heard a mile away
今晚掉落的头发火依然如此激烈极为困难，最后有70人，这是菲尔和听到一英里远
931 a.m. Without warning
931上午没有警告
explosion Roxanne for the New York community
爆炸罗克珊为纽约社区
people
人
huge explosion with a train that exploded
巨大的爆炸与一列火车发生爆炸
200 firefighters responding
200消防队员回应
explosion buildings at 15 apartments one had a piano store the other home to a church now reduce trouble and blowing smoke
在15公寓一次爆炸的建筑物有一台钢琴存放别家去教堂现在减少麻烦和吹烟
I was really working for my son in the sauna 10 minutes before the blast happened
我是真的在桑拿浴室10分钟工作为我的儿子在爆炸发生之前，
how to find neighbors
如何找到邻居
what's the least pass to the barricades ceiling of the areas to try to find your cousins
什么是最通行证等领域的路障天花板，试图找到您的表兄弟
gas leak cause the blast minutes before the explosion on their way
在他们的途中爆炸前的爆炸分钟煤气泄漏引起
this is a tragedy of the worst kinda cuz there was no indication
这是有点最差的一个悲剧的Cuz没有任何迹象
in time
及时
to save people we know we lost two people already
救人，我们知道我们失去了两个人已经
who is left the building with his family minutes before the explosion you said you smell gas just yesterday it was a month ago
谁是你说你闻到煤气味就在昨天，那是一个月前在爆炸前离开大楼与他的家人分钟
I'm a little you could walk into the building take two steps down feeling lost without
我有点，你可以走进大楼分两步走下来的感觉不输
are the neighbourhood 6000 a family
是居委会6000家
are not able to go home and many more lost everything
不能回家，还有更多失去了一切
is really Macedon intense and the impact is widespread there still here trying to get the situation completely under control their also tonight
真的是马其顿激烈，影响是普遍的还有这里试图得到完全控制局势他们今晚也
under control
在控制之下
thank you so much for your putting on the story time in San Francisco tonight investigator
非常感谢你对你的推杆在旧金山今晚研究者故事时间
terminis welding where was the cause of a huge fire pit or to an apartment complex under construction completely and dolphin get inflamed late yasterday afternoon
terminis焊接在那里有一个巨大的火坑或在建的公寓大楼完全和海豚的事业得到发炎晚yasterday下午
Milton visible from miles in nearby buildings were evacuated this battle the plants for hours to firefighters suffered minor injuries
米尔顿从附近的建筑物英里可见被疏散这场战斗几个小时​​消防队员植物受轻伤
initial solidarity today President Obama met with Ukraine's acting prime minister at the White House is a quart Russia Senator John McCain meantime plant Salida delegation of lawmakers to Ukraine tomorrow
最初的团结今天奥巴马总统会见了乌克兰的作用在白宫首相是一夸脱立法者的明天俄罗斯联邦参议员约翰·麦凯恩与此同时厂萨利达代表团前往乌克兰
tonight we can you are special NBC News coverage on Sirius children of War more than one hundred forty thousand people have been killed so far
今晚我们可以是特殊的NBC新闻报道战争的天狼星儿童超过14万的人被杀害至今
is the war began their 3 years ago this week at least ten thousand in heaven children with many thousand war wounded and there is no end in sight
在战争开始了他们3年前这个星期至少10000在天堂的孩子有许多千年战争中受伤并没有在看不到尽头
we have a port now from both sides of series border with Bill million Damascus and chief medical editor Dr Nancy Snyderman in Lebanon on the groin medical crisis among refugees there begin to mask a building
我们有一个端口现在从一系列边界两侧与比尔万元大马士革兼首席医学编辑南茜斯奈德曼博士在黎巴嫩的难民中腹股沟医疗危机有开始掩盖建筑物
60.wav
good evening underwater a startling moment for some children here in Damascus today it's not unusual but it shows why the casualty rate for children in this world
晚上好水下一个令人吃惊的时刻，一些孩子在这里大马士革今天它的不寻常，但它说明了为什么伤亡率在这个世界上的孩子
are among the highest ever recorded in the Middle East what was unusual today was to see serious later in public for the first time in months
都属于有史以来在中东地区最高的今天，是不寻常的是在公共后来看到严肃的，第一次在月
President Assad men women and children of the promised them help but it's his troops to Griffin most Koreans from their homes this family now live in a box on a sidewalk 6 children who escaped
阿萨德总统男人妇女和儿童的答应他们帮助，但它是他的部队格里芬大多数韩国人从他们的家园这个家庭现在住在一个盒子人行道上6个孩子谁逃脱
deadly see their father suffering a stroke 18 year old not there breadwinner their sister kidnapped at 14
致命看到自己的父亲患中风的18岁不是有养家糊口的妹妹被绑架14
is broken says her mother I wonder if she's cold or hungry I just want her back childlike here could be frugal living in a park in Philly
坏了说，她的母亲，我不知道她是感冒了或饿了，我只想她回来稚气这里可能是节俭的生活在费城的一个公园
send War pray to disease
发送战争祈祷疾病
suits cares but she says then a black
西装关心，但她说，随后一辆黑色
Fullerton here we just want to have fun he says send another boys but its not over it's not far away
富登在这里我们只是想有乐趣，他说再派男孩，但它不是在它的不远处
shells are raining on a c10
壳下雨的C10
can the playground let's go a mansion
可以在操场上让我们去一个豪宅
they don't know which way to turn
他们不知道该走哪条路
war is New Caney innocence here is being ripped from a generation
战争是新凯尼清白这里是从一代被撕开
NBC News Damascus
NBC新闻大马士革
im Dr Nancy Snyderman interne Lebanon
IM博士南希斯奈德曼内部黎巴嫩
parallel to the Syrian border to check up on a woman we met yesterday check out of the hospital against medical advice just 3 hours after giving birth to new baby word has it that she's not feeling well so we're going to go to this refugee camp to check on her and her living conditions
平行于叙利亚边境检查上我们遇见了昨天核对医嘱医院出新词的婴儿在分娩后短短3个小时的女人有它，她的身体不舒服，所以我们打算去这个难民营检查她和她的生活条件
the refugee camp refine 28-year-old Miriam just soom is isolated bitterly cold and the conditions deplorable it's the worst I've seen she shares a small town family now 5 children including the baby born born yesterday
难民营细化28岁的仪只是SOOM是孤立的严寒和恶劣的条件，这是我见过的她分享一个小城镇的家庭现在5岁以下儿童包括婴儿出生出生昨日最差
does no insulation chest plastic people are living in between their homeland in a country that is housing them but still not citizens her husband after taxes in CA
确实没有保温箱塑料人都生活在自己的家园之间在被安置他们的国家，但仍然不是公民丈夫税款后的CA
Miriam flying on a sin dance mattress lying next to her is her newborn length
仪飞行的罪舞蹈床垫躺在她旁边的是她刚出生的长度
the sound that your hearing is raindrops
您的听力是雨滴的声音
I guess I'll make a few minutes ago when the lights went out for the 38000 children were born in Lebanon federal halfway to start a new life
我想我会做一个几分钟前，当灯灭了的38000孩子出生在黎巴嫩联邦半路开始新的生活
Miriam describe swimming pools exhausted and just lousy for husband medicine prescribed by one of the doctors
仪形容游泳池用尽，只是糟糕由一个医生处方药的丈夫
this is so muddy with no drainage and yet the person who owns this land is charged with people hear 400 dollars a year to be here that doesn't sound like a lot of money so when you have none is an astronomical price
这是如此的泥泞，没有排水，但谁拥有这片土地的人被控的人听到了一年400块钱能在这里听起来并不像很多钱，所以，当你有没有是一个天价
there is no happy ending here just reminders everywhere that in this ongoing crisis children's lives are on the line
没有快乐的结局在这里只是催无处不在这个持续不断的危机儿童的生活就行了
in the last 48 hours missing moments of joy like this newborn nursery outside a cold drenching pouring rain tonight
在过去48小时外的冷淋浇雨今晚缺少欢乐的时刻，这样的新生儿室
on going this result for so many of the Syrian refugee children ideas for the little girl with the polio like symptoms diagnosis will keep tabs on her updates summer stateside
要去这个结果对于这么多的叙利亚难民儿童的想法与样症状诊断小儿麻痹症的小女孩将紧贴在她更新的夏天在美国本土
besides series Border tonight in massaman reporting there a number organizations working at great interest to help Syria children does information about many of the sights on our website tonight at nbcnews.com
除了一系列边境今晚在玛沙曼报告有一些机构在巨大利益的工作，以帮助叙利亚孩子确实对许多景点的信息，今晚上我们的网站nbcnews.com
steelhead tonight rescue mission
虹鳟今晚救援任务
CJ to be stolen car child trapped inside with a stranger and later
CJ被盗车的孩子被困在一个陌生人，后来
Blizzard on the moon tonight May contraction Scrabble for millions of people as yet another big storm hit hard
今晚暴雪在月球上的月收缩拼字游戏以百万计的人民的又一大风暴重创
outside Denver a 4 year old boys back with the family tonight in a suspect is in custody following a dangerous police chase in bullit in the middle of the morning rush hour is it all played out on live television get more Nelson BC Miguel Almaguer
丹佛外面一个4岁的男孩回来了，今晚在犯罪嫌疑人家属在拘留后一个危险的警察追捕中BULLIT在早晨上班高峰时间的中间是它全部发挥出来的电视直播获得更多的纳尔逊BC米格尔Almaguer
chase apparently somebody took are in Longmont
追逐显然有人把当前的位置朗蒙特
he's gone both left shoulder and right shoulder police gave the suspect through this guy is going like a rocket ship. For the safety of a 4 year old boy inside the stolen car the chase lasted over an hour to call his car jacked a silver band
他走了两个左肩和右肩警方通过这家伙会像火箭船给了犯罪嫌疑人。对于一个4岁的男孩偷走车内的安全追逐持续了一个小时打电话给他的车抬高银乐队
the suspects told 3 vehicle
犯罪嫌疑人告诉3车辆
helicopter over head
直升机在头上
Amanda's Lehigh Raiders speed veteran koaa news reporter John Morrissey is never seen anything like it
阿曼达的利哈伊攻略速度老将KOAA记者约翰·莫里西是从来没有见过这样的事情
even thinking about stopping
甚至考虑停止
it could have been is bad is your Magic Man EP Paslode school buses he was in traffic he was going wrong way on the interstate for like 15 mile
它本来可以是坏的是你的魔人的EP PASLODE校车，他在交通，他打算在州际公路上像15英里错误的方法
YouTube on the car more than half a dozen cars were doing over a hundred miles an hour easily state trooper Bellemont he was hit in seriously injure
YouTube的上车超过半打的车都做了一百英里的时速轻松州警察Bellemont他被击中的严重伤害
the car chase ended with this collision
在汽车追逐与此碰撞结束
police have their man be a suspect is on his stomach this is over
警方有他们的人是犯罪嫌疑人是他的肚子上，这是在
tonight 28 yr old Ryan stone is in custody
今晚28岁老赖安的石头是在羁押
4 year old boy clutching a teddy bear is safe back with his family
4岁的男孩抓着一个玩具熊是安全的回来与他的家人
wild pursuit that played out on my TV do you Miguel Almaguer NBC News Los Angeles
即发挥出我的电视对野生追求你米格尔Almaguer NBC新闻洛杉矶
and when we come back just 8 days till spring another
当我们回来的短短8天，直到另一个春天
big hit in the womb winter for millions of people
在子宫内的冬季以百万计的人很大的打击
there was a huge storm on the move tonight from the Midwest into the northeast blizzard like whiteout conditions making for treacherous
有一个巨大的风暴在今晚的举动从中西部到东北部暴风雪像白化条件作出的奸诈
millions of people 40 say weather is to blame for the deadly 50 vehicle pile up involve in several tractor trailers on the Ohio Turnpike
数以百万计的人40说天气是怪致命的50车辆堆积涉及的俄亥俄州高速公路几个拖拉机拖车
two people were killed and rescue workers are still trying to reach people who made the trap
两个人死亡，救援人员仍在努力达到人谁做的陷阱
Weather Channel meteorologist Mike Seidel is in upstate New York night North Rochester what is you can see right in the thick of the storm I could eating pussy
天气频道的气象学家迈克·赛德尔是在纽约州北部的夜北罗切斯特什么是你可以在厚厚的风暴，我可以吃的猫见右
500 mean to you have a snow whipping when conditions to the storm here in western New York State snow today in Chicago Detroit state didn't get the blues and women stuck in the middle of my chest Irwin Salt Lake Ontario
500的意思是你有一个雪鞭打条件时，今天在这里纽约州西部的雪风暴在芝加哥底特律的状态并没有得到停留在我的胸口欧文盐湖安大略省中部的蓝色和女人
50 miles an hour with heavy snow
每小时50英里大雪
sunspots
太阳黑子
and tonight in Morris Illinois the forecast if your a sphere shape over a foot of snow will fall
今晚在伊利诺伊州莫里斯的预测，如果你的一个球体形状在脚下的雪将下降
at least probably few complaints on to the small cold snowy winter in Boston
到小感冒多雪的冬天在波士顿至少大概很少投诉
thank you so much my federal and get inside thank you so much
太谢谢你了我的联邦进去太谢谢你了
tired US Army colonel Olema is has died he was a recipient of the Medal of Honor for his actions in the Korean War the son of a sharecropper
累了美国陆军上校旅游Olema是已经死了，他是荣誉的勋章为他的行动收件人在朝鲜战争中一个佃农的儿子
Robert from Alabama have all of your for combat and receive a medal for defending his men and holding back the enemy during the day long attack on their outpost
罗伯特从阿拉巴马州拥有所有你的战斗并获得金牌捍卫他的人，并在他们的前哨，终日攻击期间保持了敌人
despite his own worst 10 or more enemies soldier single handedly you later served 3 tours of duty as a green beret in Vietnam overly miles with 82 years old
尽管他自己最糟糕的10个或更多的敌人士兵一手您后来担任职务3旅游作为一种绿色贝雷帽在越南过于公里与82岁
what is that thing 74 Living recipes of the Medal of Honor
那是什么东西了勋章的74生活食谱
and when we come back one woman's online
当我们回来的一名女子的在线